Guide to the American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA), New York Local Records WAG.282
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI: Negotiations
  - WQXR-FM for 1977-1981, Jun-Aug 1977 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - WQXR-FM for 1977-1981, Sep-Dec 1977 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - WQXR-FM for 1977-1981, 1978-1981 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - WQXR-FM for 1981-1984 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - WQXR-FM for 1981-1984, 1982-1983 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - WQXR-FM for 1984-1987, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - WRFM-WNYW for 1966-1967 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - WRFM-WNYW for 1967-1969/1970, Jan-Jun 1967 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - WRFM-WNYW for 1967-1969/1970, Jul-Dec 1967 (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - WRFM-WNYW for 1969-1972, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - WRFM-WNYW for 1969-1972 (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - WRFM-WNYW for 1972-1973 (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - WRFM-WNYW for 1973-1974 (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - WRFM Radio for 1974-1977 (1973-1976) (Box 91, Folder 20)
  - WRFM Radio for 1977-1980 (Box 91, Folder 21)
  - WRFM Radio for 1980-1983, 1979-1981 (Box 91, Folder 22)
  - WRFM Radio for 1980-1983: Correspondence, Conflict of Interest, and other Issues, 1982 (Box 91, Folder 23)
  - WRFM Radio for 1983-1986 (Box 91, Folder 24)
  - WRKL Radio, Rockland County, 1981 (Box 91, Folder 25)
  - WRNW for 1977-1980 (Box 91, Folder 26)
  - WRVR-FM, 1975-1976 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - WRVR-FM for 1977-1980, 1977-1978 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - WRVR-FM for 1977-1980 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - [WRVR-FM] WHKH for 1981-1984, 1980-1981 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - WSNL UHF 67, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - WSTC-AM/WYRS-FM, Stanford, Connecticut, 1978-1979 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - WTFM for 1965-1969, Jan-Jul 1965 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - WTFM for 1965-1969, Sep-Dec 1965 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - WTFM for 1965-1969, 1966 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - WTFM for 1969-1972, 1968-1969 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - WTFM for 1975-1978, 1974-1976 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - WTFM for 1978-1981, 1977-1979 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - WTFM for 1982-1984, 1981 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - WTFM for 1982-1984 (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - WTTG-TV, Washington D.C. for 1970-1974 (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - WVNJ AM/FM for 1948-1949 (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - WVNJ AM/FM for 1948-1949, 1949-1950 (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - WVNJ AM/FM for 1952-1953, 1951-1952 (Box 92, Folder 18)
  - WVNJ AM/FM for 1953-1954 (Box 92, Folder 19)
  - WVNJ AM/FM for 1954-1956, 1954-1955 (Box 92, Folder 20)
  - WVNJ AM/FM for 1956-1958 (Box 92, Folder 21)
  - WVNJ AM/FM for 1959-1961 (Box 92, Folder 22)
  - WVNJ AM/FM for 1961-1964, 1961-1962 (Box 92, Folder 23)
  - WVNJ for 1964-1967 (Box 92, Folder 24)
  - WVNJ for 1967-1970 (Box 92, Folder 25)
  - WVNJ for 1967-1970, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 26)
  - WVNJ for 1970-1973, 1969-1970 (Box 92, Folder 27)
  - WVNJ for 1970-1973, 1971-1972 (Box 92, Folder 28)
  - WVNJ for 1973-1976 (Box 92, Folder 29)
  - WVNJ for 1976-1978 (Box 92, Folder 30)
  - WVNJ for 1978-1979 (Box 92, Folder 31)
  - WVNJ for 1979-1982, 1980 (Box 92, Folder 32)
  - WVNJ for 1982-1985, 1983 (Box 92, Folder 33)
  - WVOS Radio, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 34)
  - WVOX for 1973-1976 (Box 92, Folder 35)
  - WWDJ for 1972-1975 (Box 92, Folder 36)
  - WWDJ for 1975-1978 (Box 92, Folder 37)
  - WWDJ for 1978-1981, 1980 (Box 92, Folder 38)
  - WWRL for 1966-1969, 1965 (Box 92, Folder 39)
  - WWRL for 1966-1969, Jan-May 1966 (Box 92, Folder 40)
  - WWRL for 1966-1969, Jul-Dec 1966 (Box 92, Folder 41)
  - WWRL for 1966-1969, 1967-1968 (Box 92, Folder 42)
  - WWRL for 1969-1972 (Box 92, Folder 43)
  - WWRL for 1969-1972, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 44)
  - WWRL for 1972-1975, 1971 (Box 92, Folder 45)
  - WWRL for 1972-1975 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - WWRL for 1972-1975, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - WWRL for 1975-1978 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - WWRL for 1978-1981, 1978, 1980 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - WWRL for 1981-1984 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - WWRL for 1984-1987, 1983-1984 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - WXLO, 1974-1976 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - WXTV for 1968-1971 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - WXTV for 1971-1974, 1972 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - WXTV for 1976-1979, 1976, 1978 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - WXTV for 1979-1981, Jan-Mar 1979 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - WXTV for 1979-1981, Apr 1979-Dec 1980 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - WXTV for 1982-1984, 1981-1982 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - WXTV for 1982-1984, 1983-1984 (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - WXTV for 1985-1988, 1984-1986 (Box 93, Folder 15)
  - WXTV: "Nueva York Ahora", 1982-1984 (Box 93, Folder 16)
  - WYNY [An NBC Company], 1979-1981 (Box 93, Folder 17)
- Series VII: Other Unions/Guilds/Federations
  Files are arranged alphabetically by the full name of the organization, not its acronym.
  This series contains correspondence, by-laws, handbooks, legal records, organizational constitutions, and financial statements documenting AFTRA's relationships and interactions with domestic and international unions, guilds, and federations representing a variety of entertainers and performers.
  - Actors and Announcers Equity Association of Australia, 1976-1983 (Box 93, Folder 18)
  - Actors' Equity Association (AEA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 19)
  - Actors' Equity Association (AEA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1972-1973 (Box 93, Folder 20)
  - Actors' Equity Association (AEA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1975-1976 (Box 93, Folder 21)
  - Actors' Equity Association (AEA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1977 (Box 93, Folder 22)
  - Actors' Equity Association (AEA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1978 (Box 93, Folder 23)
  - Actors' Equity Association (AEA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1979 (Box 93, Folder 24)
  - Actors' Equity Association (AEA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1980 (Box 93, Folder 25)
  - Actors' Equity Association (AEA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1981 (Box 93, Folder 26)
  - Actors' Equity Association (AEA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1982 (Box 93, Folder 27)
  - Actors' Equity Association (AEA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1983-1984 (Box 93, Folder 28)
  - Actors' Equity Association (AEA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1985 (Box 93, Folder 29)
  - Actors' Equity Association (AEA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1986-1987 (Box 93, Folder 30)
  - Actors' Equity Association (AEA): Handbook, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 31)
  - American Federation of Musicians (AFM): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1947-1968 (Box 93, Folder 32)
  - American Federation of Musicians (AFM): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1969-1971 (Box 93, Folder 33)
  - American Federation of Musicians (AFM): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1972-1974 (Box 93, Folder 34)
  - American Federation of Musicians (AFM): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1975-1977 (Box 93, Folder 35)
  - American Federation of Musicians (AFM): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1978-1979 (Box 93, Folder 36)
  - American Federation of Musicians (AFM): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1980-1987 (Box 93, Folder 37)
  - American Federation of Musicians (AFM): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1988-1993 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - American Federation of Musicians (AFM): Phonograph Record Labor Agreement, 1975 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - American Federation of Musicians (AFM): Press Clippings, 1953 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - American Federation of Musicians (AFM): Wage Scales and Conditions in the Symphony Orchestra, 1974-1975 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - American Guild of Musical Artists (AGMA): Agreement, Constitution, and By-Laws, 1980 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - American Guild of Musical Artists (AGMA): Agreement with New York City Opera, 1979-1982 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - American Guild of Musical Artists (AGMA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1968 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - American Guild of Musical Artists (AGMA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1981-1983 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - American Guild of Musical Artists (AGMA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1984-1986 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - American Guild of Musical Artists (AGMA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1988-1993 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - American Guild of Musical Artists (AGMA): Handbook, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - American Guild of Musical Artists (AGMA): Pension Benefits, 1976 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - American Guild of Musical Artists (AGMA): Welfare Benefits, 1978 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - American Guild of Variety Artists (AGVA), 1971-1982 (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Associated Actors and Artistes of America (AAAA): Constitution, 1965 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Associated Actors and Artistes of America (AAAA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1977-1982 (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - Associated Actors and Artistes of America (AAAA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1983-1984 (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - Associated Actors and Artistes of America (AAAA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1987 (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - Associated Actors and Artistes of America (AAAA): Financial Statements, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Associated Actors and Artistes of America (AAAA): Financial Statements and Supplementary Information, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - Association of Canadian Television and Radio Artists (ACTRA), 1968 (Box 94, Folder 21)
  - British Actors' Equity Association: Agreement for the Employment of Performers in Television Commercials, 1986 (Box 94, Folder 22)
  - British Actors' Equity Association: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1971-1975 (Box 94, Folder 23)
  - British Actors' Equity Association: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1976-1979 (Box 94, Folder 24)
  - British Actors' Equity Association: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1980-1992 (Box 94, Folder 25)
  - British Actors' Equity Association: Regulations for the Employment of Performers in Commercials, 1971 (Box 94, Folder 26)
  - British Actors' Equity Association: Report of Approved Closed Shop in Theatre, Independent Television and Film, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 27)
  - Dansk Artist Forbund, 1985-1986 (Box 94, Folder 28)
  - Federacion de Trabajodores del Espectaculo del Paraguay, 1975-1976 (Box 94, Folder 29)
  - Federation Internationale des Auteurs (FIA): Code Principles and Declarations, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 30)
  - Federation Internationale des Auteurs (FIA): Collective Agreements for English Speaking Members in Film, 1985 (Box 94, Folder 31)
  - Federation Internationale des Auteurs (FIA): Congresses, 1973-1974 (Box 94, Folder 32)
  - Federation Internationale des Auteurs (FIA): Congresses, 1976 (Box 94, Folder 33)
  - Federation Internationale des Auteurs (FIA): Congresses, 1982 (Box 94, Folder 34)
  - Federation Internationale des Auteurs (FIA): Congresses, 1985 (Box 94, Folder 35)
  - Federation Internationale des Auteurs (FIA): Congresses, 1987 (Box 94, Folder 36)
  - Federation Internationale des Auteurs (FIA): Constitution, undated (Box 94, Folder 37)
  - Federation Internationale des Auteurs (FIA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1971 (Box 94, Folder 38)
  - Federation Internationale des Auteurs (FIA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1972 (Box 94, Folder 39)
  - Federation Internationale des Auteurs (FIA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 40)
  - Federation Internationale des Auteurs (FIA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 41)
  - Federation Internationale des Auteurs (FIA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1975 (Box 94, Folder 42)
  - Federation Internationale des Auteurs (FIA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1976-1977 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Federation Internationale des Auteurs (FIA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1981 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Federation Internationale des Auteurs (FIA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1982 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Federation Internationale des Auteurs (FIA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1983 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Federation Internationale des Auteurs (FIA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1984 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Federation Internationale des Auteurs (FIA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1985 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Federation Internationale des Auteurs (FIA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1986 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Federation Internationale des Auteurs (FIA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1987 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Federation Internationale des Auteurs (FIA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1988 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Federation Internationale des Auteurs (FIA): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1991-1993 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Federation Internationale des Auteurs (FIA): Symposium, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Federation Internationale des Musicians (FIM): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1985 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Interchangeability, 1957-1958 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Interchangeability, 1961-1963 (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - Interchangeability, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - Interchangeability, 1965 (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - Interchangeability, 1975 (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - Interchangeability, 1977-1979 (Box 95, Folder 18)
  - Interchangeability, 1980-1982 (Box 95, Folder 19)
  - Interchangeability, 1983-1985 (Box 95, Folder 20)
  - Interchangeability, 1986-1987 (Box 95, Folder 21)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employment (IATSE): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1971-1979 (Box 95, Folder 22)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employment (IATSE): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1980-1990 (Box 95, Folder 23)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employment (IATSE): Electronics Supplemental Basic Agreement, 1976 (Box 95, Folder 24)
  - International Secretariat of Entertainment Trade Unions (ISETU): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1971 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - International Secretariat of Entertainment Trade Unions (ISETU): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1972 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - International Secretariat of Entertainment Trade Unions (ISETU): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - International Secretariat of Entertainment Trade Unions (ISETU): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - International Secretariat of Entertainment Trade Unions (ISETU): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1975-1980 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - International Secretariat of Entertainment Trade Unions (ISETU): Correspondence and Related Materials, 1986-1991 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - International Secretariat of Entertainment Trade Unions (ISETU): Report of Third International Congress, 1971 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Irish Actors' Equity, 1981-1988 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Japan Actors Union: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1970-1973 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Japan Actors Union: Policies, 1948 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - La Asociacion Puerto Riquena de Artistas y Tecnicos del Espectaculo (APATE), 1971-1990 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Labor Council for Latin American Advancement, 1975-1979 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Merger: AFTRA Coordinating Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Merger: AFTRA Coordinating Committee, 1978 (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - Merger: AFTRA/AGMA Committee, 1980 (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - Merger: AFTRA/AGMA Committee, 1981 (Box 96, Folder 16)
  - Merger: AFTRA/AGMA Committee, 1982 (Box 96, Folder 17)
  - Merger: AFTRA/AGMA Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 96, Folder 18)
  - Merger: AGMA, Correspondence and Related Materials, 1980-1982 (Box 96, Folder 19)
  - Merger: AGMA, Financial Statements, 1976-1979 (Box 96, Folder 20)
  - Merger: AGMA, Systems Analysis Procedure Flow, 1982 (Box 96, Folder 21)
  - Merger: General Correspondence, 1980-1985 (Box 96, Folder 22)
  - Merger: Joint AFTRA-SAG Coordinating Committee, 1980 (Box 96, Folder 23)
  - Merger: Joint AFTRA-SAG Coordinating Committee, Jan-May 1981 (Box 96, Folder 24)
  - Merger: Joint AFTRA-SAG Coordinating Committee, Jun-Dec 1981 (Box 96, Folder 25)
  - Merger: Joint AFTRA-SAG Coordinating Committee, 1982 (Box 96, Folder 26)
  - Merger: Joint AFTRA-SAG Coordinating Committee, 1983 (Box 96, Folder 27)
  - National Association of Broadcasters (NAB), 1971-1986 (Box 96, Folder 28)
  - National Association of Interpreters (ANDI), 1975 (Box 96, Folder 29)
  - National Union of Actors and Directors: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1975 (Box 96, Folder 30)
  - Negro Actors Guild of America (NAG), 1943-1977 (Box 96, Folder 31)
  - Norsk Skuespillerforbund, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 32)
  - Osterreichische Kunstlerunion, 1976 (Box 96, Folder 33)
  - Screen Actors Guild: Agency Regulations, 1969 (Box 96, Folder 34)
  - Screen Actors Guild: Codified Basic Agreement, 1977 (Box 96, Folder 35)
  - Screen Actors Guild: Commercials Contract, 1963 (Box 96, Folder 36)
  - Screen Actors Guild: Commercials Contract, 1972 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Screen Actors Guild: Commercials Contract, 1979 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Screen Actors Guild: Constitution and By-Laws, 1980 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Screen Actors Guild: Contract Digest, 1983-1985 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Screen Actors Guild: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1966-1968 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Screen Actors Guild: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1969-1979 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Screen Actors Guild: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1980 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Screen Actors Guild: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1981 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Screen Actors Guild: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1982 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Screen Actors Guild: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1983 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Screen Actors Guild: Correspondence and Related Materials, Jan-May 1984 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Screen Actors Guild: Correspondence and Related Materials, Jun-Dec 1984 (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Screen Actors Guild: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1985 (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Screen Actors Guild: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1986 (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Screen Actors Guild: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1987 (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - Screen Actors Guild: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1988 (Box 97, Folder 16)
  - Screen Actors Guild: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1989 (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - Screen Actors Guild: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1990 (Box 97, Folder 18)
  - Screen Actors Guild: Industrial Contract, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 19)
  - Screen Actors Guild: Information Systems Requirements Proposal, 1985 (Box 97, Folder 20)
  - Screen Actors Guild: New York Branch Rules and Procedures, 1953 (Box 97, Folder 21)
  - Screen Actors Guild: New York Branch Rules and Procedures, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 22)
  - Screen Actors Guild: New York Extra Players Agreement, 1980 (Box 97, Folder 23)
  - Screen Actors Guild: New York Extras Television Commercials Agreement, 1963-1966 (Box 97, Folder 24)
  - Screen Actors Guild: Producers Codified Basic Agreement, 1967 (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Screen Actors Guild: Producers Codified Basic Agreement, 1977 (Box 97, Folder 26)
  - Screen Actors Guild: Producers Industrial and Educational Contract, 1982 (Box 97, Folder 27)
  - Screen Actors Guild: Supplement to Producer Codified Basic Agreement, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 28)
  - Screen Actors Guild: Systems Improvement Project Proposal, 1985 (Box 97, Folder 29)
  - Screen Actors Guild: Television Agreement, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 30)
  - Screen Actors Guild: Television Agreement, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 31)
  - Screen Extras Guild (SEG): Television Commercials Agreement, 1969 (Box 97, Folder 32)
  - Sindicato Nacional de Trabajadores de la Muscia de la Republica Mexicana, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 33)
  - South African Theatre Union, 1974 (Box 97, Folder 34)
  - Unions for the Performing Arts, 1985-1988 (Box 97, Folder 35)
  - United Actors Association (UAA), 1977 (Box 97, Folder 36)
  - Writers Guild of America, 1981 (Box 97, Folder 37)
- Series VIII: Photographs
  This series consists primarily of photographs taken to be used in the New York Local's publication Stand By! Also included are several oversized photographs of early annual conventions.
  - Photographs, primarily for Stand-By (Box 98)
  - Photographs [oversize] (Box 99)